[
  {
    "question": "How long will the national anthem last?",
    "left": "1:10 and Under",
    "right": "Over 1:10",
    "answer": "unknown",
    "id": "AQfsR9xHIQmyx1jR"
  },
  {
    "question": "The coin will land on:",
    "left": "Heads",
    "right": "Tails",
    "answer": "unknown",
    "id": "PPrsFdARh5iciwad"
  },
  {
    "question": "Who will win the coin toss?",
    "left": "Bengals",
    "right": "Rams",
    "answer": "unknown",
    "id": "YeLP8gETO2XGGGPO"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which turnover will come first?",
    "left": "Fumble",
    "right": "Interception",
    "answer": "unknown",
    "id": "zDpCE8KInZIVd7JQ"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which will be the first team to lose the ball (turnover) from a Fumble or Interception?",
    "left": "Bengals",
    "right": "Rams",
    "answer": "unknown",
    "id": "P5cOk5iSYpvEUZyh"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which team will be first to be penalized?",
    "left": "Bengals",
    "right": "Rams",
    "answer": "unknown",
    "id": "SjTjIkJwMXCUUwA6"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which team will score first?",
    "left": "Bengals",
    "right": "Rams",
    "answer": "unknown",
    "id": "GYRsM1wqjLlltJOe"
  },
  {
    "question": "What will the first score will be?",
    "left": "Touchdown",
    "right": "Field Goal",
    "answer": "unknown",
    "id": "kz6jACTyC50nKTwk"
  },
  {
    "question": "Will the first touchdown be on a passing play?",
    "left": "Yes",
    "right": "No",
    "answer": "unknown",
    "id": "Jf1NUDZOp5TViUqn"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which team will have the last possession in 1st half?",
    "left": "Bengals",
    "right": "Rams",
    "answer": "unknown",
    "id": "FJYdHLpWGKwxdHpb"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which team will throw the first challenge flag?",
    "left": "Bengals",
    "right": "Rams",
    "answer": "unknown",
    "id": "6jiT0SkKKnhSk2fF"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which team will score last?",
    "left": "Bengals",
    "right": "Rams",
    "answer": "unknown",
    "id": "GhUTPjQHJq5tjqXu"
  },
  {
    "question": "Will there be a score in the final 2 minutes of game?",
    "left": "Yes",
    "right": "No",
    "answer": "unknown",
    "id": "VwsEHJ3MjvuvYMnp"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which team will have the last possession?",
    "left": "Bengals",
    "right": "Rams",
    "answer": "unknown",
    "id": "8ShgxcLifZLZsoEw"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which team will throw more interceptions?",
    "left": "Bengals",
    "right": "Rams",
    "answer": "unknown",
    "id": "0g663CWNne8rt4jw"
  },
  {
    "question": "How long will the game last, from kickoff to game end, with commercials and halftime shows?",
    "left": "3 hours and 45 minutes or less",
    "right": "Over 3 hours and 45 minutes",
    "answer": "unknown",
    "id": "a7SO2mCP8qf56kFi"
  },
  {
    "question": "During which half of the game will the most points be scored?",
    "left": "First",
    "right": "Second",
    "answer": "unknown",
    "id": "vEayHpH7riRFMTZ8"
  },
  {
    "question": "How many points will the Bengals score?",
    "left": "21 and under",
    "right": "Over 21",
    "answer": "unknown",
    "id": "6ucWiyzVVIGYFKka"
  },
  {
    "question": "How many points will the Rams score?",
    "left": "21 and under",
    "right": "Over 21",
    "answer": "unknown",
    "id": "dlTgUPl1tOU7ComR"
  },
  {
    "question": "How many points total will be scored by both teams?",
    "left": "40 and under",
    "right": "Over 40",
    "answer": "unknown",
    "id": "eoq48UygOKfpRonP"
  },
  {
    "question": "What will be the difference of points between the teams at the end of the game?",
    "left": "7 and under",
    "right": "Over 7",
    "answer": "unknown",
    "id": "3f2Gc4dFBF7ALKkZ"
  },
  {
    "question": "Will the total points scored by the Bengals be an even number or an odd number?",
    "left": "Even",
    "right": "Odd",
    "answer": "unknown",
    "id": "zQHpAGFpf4zPXruF"
  },
  {
    "question": "Will the total points scored by the Rams be an even number or an odd number?",
    "left": "Even",
    "right": "Odd",
    "answer": "unknown",
    "id": "XLgSuRbUMo9xuWrD"
  },
  {
    "question": "Who will win?",
    "left": "Bengals",
    "right": "Rams",
    "answer": "unknown",
    "id": "q84XY70Fk55BZxrr"
  }
]
